♪ MTV. ♪
♪ ♪
CARTMAN: Ow. Ow!
Ah, God!
I'm just taking
your blood pressure, Eric.
It's too tight. Stop.
(air hisses)
Ms. Cartman,
I'm extremely worried
about your son's health.
His blood pressure,
his cholesterol.
I think it's time
for some drastic measures
to bring down his weight.
Oh, God, here we go
with this shit again.
Doctor, we try to have Eric
eat right and exercise,
but it just doesn't seem
to work for him.
Well, there might be
another answer.
Have you heard of semaglutides?
Semaglutides?
They're the active ingredient
in Ozempic,
a drug originally made
for people with diabetes
but we've now discovered
they can help obese people
lose vast amounts of weight.
Really?
It's a whole new era
of medicine.
A miracle, really.
Young man, how would you like
to not be fat anymore?
Not be fat anymore?
Me?
Not fat anymore?
Towelie. Towelie.
You're not gonna believe this.
Dude, have you ever done
GLP-1 peptides?
GLP pep what now?
There's these new,
crazy drugs people are doing.
It's like cocaine and molly
mixed together.
They make women go crazy.
No, really?
Yeah. Last night I was partying
with nine hot MILFs,
and this morning I woke up,
and guess what.
I don't feel like total shit.
It's like a miracle drug.
You partied all night and
felt fine the next morning?
Totally fine.
There's, like,
nothing wrong with me.